http://www.bwire.com/privacy-policy.html

Call:(800) 631-0490Fax: (973) 239-3985sales@bwire.com
HomeAbout UsMaterialsResourcesProduct CatalogContact UsRequest InformationOnline Order / Inquiry Form
Wire Cloth, Wire Mesh and Woven WireCertified Manufacturer of Custom Wire Cloth, Wire Mesh and Woven Wire made of Stainless Steel and Other Corrosion Resistant Alloys.View OurONLINE CATALOG
Capabilities / ProductsWoven Wire ClothFilter Wire ClothWelded Wire ClothDisc & Sample SetsWeaving and
FabricationResourcesCustomer SupportOrdering InfoOnline Order /
Inquiry FormContact UsCertifications
& RegistrationsISO 9001:2015Nadcap
- Welding / BrazingDirectorate of Defense
Trade Controls
Printable PageEmail This Page
Privacy PolicyBelleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc. respects your privacy and the purpose for which our site visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.Information Collected
If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via the "mail to:" function or filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only the policy of Belleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc.'s website and not sites that users access via links from our site. Belleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc. is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.Cookies
Belleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc. website does not use cookies. Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
Belleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that Belleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.This policy statement is made in the name of Belleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc. and is effective as of December 23, 2010. This statement does not create an agreement between Belleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party. Contact Us:
Belleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc.
18 Rutgers Avenue
Cedar Grove, NJ 07009
Toll-Free: (800) 631-0490
Phone: (973) 239-0074
Fax: (973) 239-3985
Email: sales@bwire.com
Website: www.bwire.com
www.bwire.comBelleville Wire Cloth Co., Inc.|18 Rutgers Ave., Cedar Grove, NJ 07009|Toll-Free: (800) 631-0490|Ph: (973) 239-0074|Fx: (973) 239-3985|E-mail: sales@bwire.com
Terms of Sale  |  Terms and Conditions of Purchase |  Privacy  |  Sitemap    Site created by ThomasNet Web Solutions and powered by Navigator Platform
